But always in a vacant and representative way of course
Should the lady to Stureplan
Yes
Then you have to go home and put on a little shorter skirt so you get some looks at you
Unless the girls show some skin then they risk getting to hell
That is, a rental apartment on Upper Gärdet with any middle -class guy
They believe in a single interpretation of by the nobility calendar
And questioning anyone who does not think it is important
In the summer you need to pilgrimage to Saint-Tropez but Marbella is also holy
They follow the laws of sangria
Gyllengrip What are you doing?
I am about to inspect the bus here
The car is in the workshop
Have you heard of taxi?
My phone is broken
But rental car it is possible to rent, I have put it myself
But there are those who work against radicalization
Johan af Klintenstjärna has started the organization neither middle class nor comrade upset
Many young are radicalized in the closed upper -class gang and go to ice
Ice?
Boarding schools
And that radicalization is a problem
Showed the reactions after the middle -class artist Nils Larsson failed to depict the king at one of his latest works of art
Tastered
Long live the king
Complete scandal
Oxel star is big
And this also applies to the upper -class organizations, several of which have been in windy weather
It is scandalous that Sweden's young landlord invited Fredrik von Knagelberg to the aristocrat fair
He has, among other things, advocated orderly side legs and wrist watches from the age of five
He also has connections to money -haunting extremism
Johan has been called everything from class traitors to caravan veins
He lives today under threat of not being allowed to participate in the pheasant act
But his struggle continues
The solution is not more oyster bars for the young
We have to start questioning destructive ideas from several hundred years back in time
Next week
Religious fundamentalists control the district
Resist your sinful lusts
It is challenging dance and swearing up there
Move
We pray for you
Forgive them God, for your strength to ward off desires such as kisses and caress